Products

[Technology lookup

Find out what websites are built with](https://www.wappalyzer.com/lookup/)

* * *

[Lead lists

Create a list of sites for a technology, keyword or domain](https://www.wappalyzer.com/lists/)

* * *

[Email verification

Verify the validity of any email address](https://www.wappalyzer.com/verify/)

* * *

[Keyword search

Find websites by keyword](https://www.wappalyzer.com/websites/)

* * *

[Website alerts

Monitor websites for technology changes](https://www.wappalyzer.com/alerts/)

* * *

[Apps

Connect Wappalyzer to the apps you use](https://www.wappalyzer.com/apps/)

Resources

[Technologies

Browse technologies and categories](https://www.wappalyzer.com/technologies/)

* * *

[Articles

Free content covering technographics](https://www.wappalyzer.com/articles/)

* * *

[FAQs

Answers to frequently asked questions](https://www.wappalyzer.com/faq/lists/)

* * *

[Documentation

API reference and developer documentation](https://www.wappalyzer.com/docs/)

[Home](https://www.wappalyzer.com/)* /
Privacy policy

* * *

Privacy policy
==============

The Wappalyzer privacy policy describes how we treat personal information when you use our website, software and APIs (collectively, '**Services**').

Log data
--------

As with most websites and technology services delivered over the internet, our servers automatically collect information when you access or use our Services and record it in log files. This log data may include the internet protocol (IP) address, the date and time the Services were used, browser type and settings and cookie data.

Account registration
--------------------

When you open an account, you provide us with personal information that includes your email address and a password. You can also choose to add a billing address to your account. You can delete your information and cancel your account at any time.

Browser extension
-----------------

You do not need to provide any personal information in order to download and use the [browser extension](https://www.wappalyzer.com/apps/) .

We do not track your browsing behaviour or any information that can be traced back to you personally.

The Wappalyzer browser extension periodically sends information about websites you visit to our servers. This information includes domain names, anonymised URLs and the names of identified technologies. This information may be sold to or shared with third parties. You can disable the automatic sending of information in the browser extension settings.

Gmail add-on
------------

By installing the Gmail add-on, you grant us temporary access to message meta data. We use this data to identify the domain name of sender's email addresses. This information is sent to our servers over a secure connection so that we can provide you with information about the domain, such as the technologies in use.

The use of personal data is limited to providing user-facing features. We do not store or share this information.

Sign in with Google
-------------------

When you choose to sign in with Google, we capture your email address solely for the purpose of creating your Wappalyzer account. We do not retain or use any other information from your Google account. Your email address is used exclusively for account management and communication purposes related to our Services.

* * *

Products

Use cases

Pricing

Resources

Company

* * *

* * *

Products

* * *

* * *

Resources

* * *
